https://origin-and-cause.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Origin and Cause Privacy Statement
We collect personal information from our customers in the regular course of doing business. This page answers some of your most frequently asked questions, and lets you know exactly how we are protecting the information you entrust to us.
What personal information do you collect about me?
We collect the following information about you:
Name
Address
Postal Code
Phone Number
Email Address
Product/service preferences
Opinions about products and services
When you visit our web site, we also collect:
information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of operating system and browser you use, and your computer’s location
what pages you visit on our site and what links you click on
How do you use this information?
The main reasons we collect personal information from you are:
Application/Contact us forms
Because it is required by law
Complaints
Contests/Surveys
Customer relationship management
Customer service
Marketing
Orders
To complete a sale/transaction
If it is a necessary part of any of these transactions, we may disclose your information to another company. For example, when you apply for credit, we pass on your personal information to a credit reporting agency so we can complete a credit check. We also pass on your name and address to a courier company if a delivery is required.
Use of Personal Information for Secondary Reasons
We also may use your personal information for other, secondary reasons, including:
To complete a sale/transaction
Product/service preferences
Marketing
Name
Address
Postal Code
Phone Number
Email Address
Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties
Sometimes, we also share your personal information with other companies, including:
Third party contractors (such as a courier company or customer relationship management consultant)
We will also disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so.
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, we assume you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask you for personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your consent or provide you with an opportunity to say no. Saying no is called “opting out”. By opting out, you can tell us not to collect the information and/or not to share it with other companies.
How do I opt out?
When you to receive our marketing communications, at the bottom of the email, there is link to unsubscribe if you do not want that information to be used for marketing purposes or to be shared with other companies.
How do I get more information?
Our team will be happy to answer any questions you may have about your personal information. If you would like more information about our policies, or you would like to see exactly what personal information we have about you in our records, or you wish to register a complaint, please contact:
Name: George Costandi
Address: 1336 Sandhill Drive Ancaster, Ontario L9G 4V5
Phone: 9057124100
Email: gcostandi@origin-and-cause.com
You can also contact the Privacy Commissioner of Canada for assistance between the hours of 8:30 a.m. to 4:30 p.m. est, at:
Toll-free: 1-800-282-1376 FREE
Phone: (819)994-5444
Fax: (819)994-5424
TTY: (819)994-6591
or by mail at:
30 Victoria Street
Gatineau, Quebec
K1A 1H3
or on the web at:
http://www.priv.gc.ca
You can also contact your Provincial or Territorial Privacy Commissioner’s office for more information:
Ontario
Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner of Ontario
2 Bloor Street East, Suite 1400
Toronto, Ontario M4W 1A8
Phone: (416) 326-3333
Toll-free: 1 (800) 387-0073 FREE (free within Ontario)
Email: info@ipc.on.ca
Web Site: http://www.ipc.on.ca/
